Review Exercise 11, Varying Emotions. Repeat the following statement and
response, expressing the various feelings or tones indicated in parentheses. Anger.
I told you it wouldn't work. I thought it would. Excitement. I told you it wouldn't
work. I thought it would. Disbelief. Told you it wouldn't work, and I thought it
would Smugness I told you it wouldn't work. I thought it would
Humor, I told you it wouldn't work. I thought it would Sadness I told you it
wouldn't work. I thought it would Relief I told you it wouldn't work whew I thought
it would Resignation. I told you it wouldn't work. I thought it would. Repeat
the statement using three other tones that you'd like to try. Now that you've run
through a couple of emotions and practice speaking with both meaning and feeling,
try having some two-word conversations. These are pretty common in day-to-day
situations.